What would you do to get in?
The In Crowd is a drama, mystery, thriller film directed by Mary Lambert.
A mentally disturbed young woman takes a job at a posh country club and falls in with a clique of wealthy college kids where
she's taken under the wing of the clique's twisted leader, who harbors some dark secrets too terrifying to tell.
Adrien, played by Lori Heuring.
Brittany, played by Susan Ward.
Matt, played by Matthew Settle.
Bobby, played by Nathan Bexton.
Dr. Amanda Giles, played by Tess Harper.
Kelly, played by Laurie Fortier.
The In Crowd is a 2000 American teen thriller film directed by Mary Lambert, and
starring Susan Ward, Lori Heuring, Matthew Settle, and Nathan Bexton.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.